[{"Response":"Got worse","Percentage of respondents":49.3,"Question":"Compared with this time last year, do you think that your personal financial circumstances have improved, stayed the same or got worse?","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Stayed the same","Percentage of respondents":28.7,"Question":"Compared with this time last year, do you think that your personal financial circumstances have improved, stayed the same or got worse?","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Improved","Percentage of respondents":19.9,"Question":"Compared with this time last year, do you think that your personal financial circumstances have improved, stayed the same or got worse?","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very difficult","Percentage of respondents":6.8,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Difficult","Percentage of respondents":9.6,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly difficult","Percentage of respondents":10.8,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly easy","Percentage of respondents":31.2,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Easy","Percentage of respondents":20.0,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very easy","Percentage of respondents":17.5,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very difficult","Percentage of respondents":18.0,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Difficult","Percentage of respondents":13.1,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly difficult","Percentage of respondents":17.7,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly easy","Percentage of respondents":25.1,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Easy","Percentage of respondents":13.7,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very easy","Percentage of respondents":8.8,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very difficult","Percentage of respondents":10.7,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Difficult","Percentage of respondents":11.4,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly difficult","Percentage of respondents":17.1,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly easy","Percentage of respondents":25.0,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Easy","Percentage of respondents":12.4,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very easy","Percentage of respondents":8.3,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022}]